Guide to the Cornell University Office of the Vice Provost records, 1959-1969.
Cornell University Office of the Vice Provost records, 1959-1969.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Office of the Vice Provost records, 1959-1969.
4-2-1264
Cornell University. Office of the Vice Provost.
4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, and office files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Includes correspondence, reports, and office files.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, reports, and office files concerning research grants; research facilities; computers at Cornell; departments and divisions within the University; faculty and students; faculty committees and Faculty Council; University Council; and other Cornell programs and topics.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University--Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- A, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Agway, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- B, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- C, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Center for International Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Cornell Computing Center, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Computing Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Cornell Plantations, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Cornell University News Bureau, 1965 (Box 1)
- Cornell University Water Resources Center, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Crops Science Society of America, 1965 (Box 1)
- Current Status and Future Development of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 1)
- D, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Duke Research Laboratory, 1966 (Box 1)
- E, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Empire Sugar Company, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- F, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Faculty Research Grants, 1965 (Box 1)
- Farm Electronification Council (New York), 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Farm Research, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Federal Support, 1965 (Box 1)
- Forage and Field Crops Research Task Force (interdepartmental), 1967 (Box 1)
- Ford Foundation, 1965 (Box 1)
- Foreign Agriculture Service Brochures, 1966 (Box 1)
- Foundation for American Agriculture (Box 1)
- Frank, Dr. Konstantin, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Freshman English, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
- G, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Graduate School, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Grapes, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- H, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- High School Natural Science Program, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Home Economics (Search Committee for Coordinator of Research), 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Ho Nun De Kah, 1967 (Box 1)
- Horses, 1966 (Box 1)
- Human Community Resource Task Force (Lee Taylor), 1967 (Box 1)
- I, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Industrial and Labor Relations School (N.Y.S.), 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Interdepartmental Research and Extension Programs, 1966 (Box 1)
- J, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Judging Teams, 1966 (Box 1)
- K, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- L, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Lecture Room Facilities in Plant School, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Livestock Program, 1965 (Box 1)
- Lynn, Walt - Seminars (Man's Environment), 1966 (Box 1)
- Congressman, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Governor's Office, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Secretary of Agriculture, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Secretary of the Interior, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Senators, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Mc, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- M, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Mastitis Control Project, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Mechanical Harvesting, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Dr. Joseph F. Metz, Jr., 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Microforms, 1966 (Box 1)
- Muck Crops, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- N, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- New York Farmer's Award, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- New York-Pennsylvania Agricultural Research Coordination, 1966 (Box 1)
- N.Y.S. Canners and Freezers Assn., 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- NESSD (North Eastern States Seed Development), 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Northeast Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- O, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Oral History, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Orientation Program for International Students, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Overhead Rates, 1965 (Box 1)
- P, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Cornell Pesticide Residue Research Lab, 1966 (Box 1)
- Interdepartmental Plant Science Courses, Ad Hoc Committee Report, 1966 (Box 1)
- Perservation of Agricultural Land, Commission on, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Promotions, 1961-1965 (Box 1)
- Q, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Quota Requests for Graduate School, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- R, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Regional Studies, Division of, 1965 (Box 1)
- Office of the Registrar, 1966 (Box 1)
- Research Club of Cornell, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Research Facilities at Cornell (Box 1)
- Research Grants, 1966 (Box 1)
- Research Park, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Small Animal Facility Proposal (Research Park), 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- RESEARCH - Salient Points of the Report "A National Program of Research for Agriculture", 1966 (Box 1)
- Resources Brochure, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Rural Development Program - Land-Use Conversion, 1966 (Box 1)
- Controller, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- President, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Provost, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Secretary * Treasurer, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Vice Presidents, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Circular Letters, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Dean and Directors, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Department Head's Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Agricultural Economics, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Agricultural Economics Publications, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Agronomy, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Agronomy Ponds, 1962 (Box 2)
- Animal Science, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Animal Science 360/40 Computer, 1966 (Box 2)
- Animal Science Farm, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Research Dairy Facility - Plot Plan, 1967 (Box 2)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- L.H. Bailey Papers, 1965 (Box 2)
- Biochemistry, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Bioclimatic Laboratories, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Biological Sciences, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Buildings and Properties, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Buisness Office, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Cell Laboratory, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Communication Arts, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Communication Art's Proposal for a Graduate Field, 1967 (Box 2)
- S, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- SESD, Reviewers Comments, 1960-1964 (Box 2)
- Sheep Program, 1967 (Box 2)
- Dr. E. H. Smith, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
- Spice, 1965 (Box 2)
- Soil Conservation Servicce (USDA), 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- State Appropriations, 1966 (Box 2)
- Statler, 1967 (Box 2)
- Stony Brook, 1965 (Box 2)
- Stony Kill, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- Stony Soils, 1965 (Box 2)
- Student Health Service, 1965 (Box 2)
- Student Housing, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
- Study Abroad, 1966 (Box 2)
- Study of The Current Status and Future of Development of Agriculturre and Related Industries in the State, 1967 (Box 2)
- Sugar Beets, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- Summer Session and Extramural Courses, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- SUNY, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- SUNY Budget Requests, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- SUNY - Faculty Senate and Faculty Association, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- T, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- Task Force Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Traffic Board, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
- W.K. Kennedy Travel Vouchers, Jan. 1967-Dec. 1967 (Box 2)
- Travelling Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Tyler, Win (N.Y.S. Canners and Freezers Assn.), 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- U, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- University Development Office, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- University Faculty, 1966 (Box 2)
- University Libraries, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- USDA, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- U.S. Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- V, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Distinguished Visitors and Visiting Professors, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- W, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Washington State University - Pullman, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
- Waste Disposal, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
- Water Resources, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Water Resources - Temporary State Commission on Water Resources Planning (F.E. Van Lare), 1965 (Box 2)
- Wildlife Research Unit, New York Cooperative (Box 2)
- World Food Supply Panel, 1967 (Box 2)
- XYZ, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Conservation, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Office of the Dean, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Office of Associate Dean, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
- Ecology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Education, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Entomology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Entomology Departments Ratings, 1966 (Box 3)
- Extension, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Extension Bulletins, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
- County Agricultural Agents, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- 4-H, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Extension * State Leaders Office, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Farm Services and Student Practice, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Floriculture, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Food Science, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Genetics, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Geneva - NYS Agricultural Experiment Station, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Home Economics, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- International Agricultural Development, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- IAD Reports and Proposals, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- UPCA (University of the Phillippines and Cornell), 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Proposal for Renewal and Extension of Ford Foundation Grant to the International Agricultural Development Program, Cornell University, 1967-1972 (Box 3)
- Mann Library, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Microbiology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Neurobiology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Plant Breeding, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Plant Breeding - Biometrics Unit, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Plant Breeding Field House, 1965 (Box 3)
- Plant Pathology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Pomology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Poultry Science, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Research, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Research, Agricultural in N.Y., 1964-1965 (Box 3)
- Resident Instruction, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Resident Instruction - Student Enrollment, 1964-1967 (Box 3)
- Rural Sociology, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Long Island Vegetable Farm, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Vegetable Crops, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Veterinary College, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Wiegand Herbarium, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
- Agricultural and Conservational Council, 1965 (Box 4)
- Biometry and Statistics Committee, 1966 (Box 4)
- B and PA Deanship Search Committee, 1968 (Box 4)
- Buildings and Properties Review Committees, 1965-1969 (Box 4)
- CAL, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
- University Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 4)
- College Dairy Committee, 1967 (Box 4)
- College Floriculture Committee, College Ornamental Committee, 1967 (Box 4)
- College Seed Committee, 1967 (Box 4)
- Computer Task Force Committee - College of Agricultre, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
- Conferences, Committee on, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
- Conservation Headship, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- Cornell Plantations Committee, 1968 (Box 4)
- Council for N.Y.S. College of Agriculture, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- Curriculum Committee, 1965 (Box 4)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1965-1968 (Box 4)
- Committee on Educational Program for University Staff, 1968 (Box 4)
- English Proficiency Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
- Faculty of Agricultre Meetings, 1965-1969 (Box 4)
- Faculty Committee on Public Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
- Faculty Council, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- Faculty Council - Ad Hoc Committee on the Arts, 1967 (Box 4)
- Faculty Council Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
- Food Indsutry Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 4)
- Food Science Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 4)
- Grading Manual Committee, 1965 (Box 4)
- Graduate Education at Geneva Committee, 1967 (Box 4)
- Higher Education Advisroy Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
- Human Rights, Faculty-Student Committee, 1968 (Box 4)
- Human Rights, President's Committee on, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
- IAD - Advisory Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
- Long Range Planning Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- National Academy of Science's Committee on Allocation of Agricultural Research Suport, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
- Natural Resources Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
- N.Y.S. Soil Conservation Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- N.Y.S. Soil and Water Conservation Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- Petitions Committee, 1965 (Box 4)
- Plant Pathology Review Committee, 1967 (Box 4)
- Publications Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- Research Club of Cornell, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
- Rural Education - Search Committee for Head, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
- Rural Sociology Headship Search Committee, 1966 (Box 4)
- Prof. Sear's Committee - (Role of the Dean of the Graduate School), 1965 (Box 4)
- Social Sciences Committee in College of Agriculture, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
- Sociology at Cornell, Study Committee, 1968 (Box 4)
- Special Education Projects, Committee on (COSEP), 1968 (Box 4)
- Special Projects Committee, 1968 (Box 4)
- Television Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 4)
- Undergraduate Programs Abroad - Ad Hoc Committee, 19667-1968 (Box 4)
- University Council, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
- University Lecturers, Committee on, 1967 (Box 4)
- University Faculty, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
- Willard Straight Trustee - Board of Governors, 1966-1967 (Box 4)